styleschecks.com 2016-03-26

# Privacy Policy - The Styles Check Company

## Last updated April 2014

Direct Checks Unlimited Sales, Inc. (“Direct Checks”) is committed to protecting your privacy and utilizing technology that gives you the safest and most powerful online experience available. The following information will help you understand how Direct Checks collects, uses, and safeguards the information you provide through this website. We want to assure you that when we ask for personal information, our goal is to improve customer relationships. The terms "we", "our", and "us" in this Privacy statement refer to Direct Checks Unlimited Sales, Inc. and our associated brands including The Styles Check Co.

## Information Collection & Use

We use the information collected about you to process your order and to provide a better shopping experience. We may request that you voluntarily supply personal information for purposes such as receiving correspondence, registering on a website, making purchases, participating in online surveys or market research. If you elect to participate, we may require personally identifiable information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, financial institution information, credit card information, e-mail address, or personal photos. When you submit personal information to us, you understand and agree that we may access, store, and use your information.

We may use your information to communicate with you about products, services, and future promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we offer you the option not to receive these types of communications. If you no longer wish to receive special offers or promotional notifications, please follow the unsubscribe instructions included in each communication. We may also send you order confirmation emails. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you products/services and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Information Sharing and Your Choices

| Reasons we can share your information  | Does Direct Checks Share?  | Can you limit this sharing?  
---|---|---  
For our everyday business purposes - including billing, processing transactions, & fulfilling your requests for products or services; customer & marketing support services. | Yes | No  
For our marketing purposes - to offer products and services | Yes | Yes  
For third parties to market to you | Yes | Yes  
  
We do not share, rent or sell your email address to third parties for them to market their products and services directly to you via email. We may however, selectively provide names, physical mailing addresses and other purchase information (not bank identifiers or account numbers) to reputable third parties (e.g. catalog mailers, direct mail marketing companies, and non-profit companies) whose products and services we think may interest you. These third parties are carefully screened and are aware of our privacy policy.

We share your personal information with companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order, billing processing or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We reserve the right to disclose information about you:

  * As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process,
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.
  * If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

## Security

We are committed to protecting your personal information. Security measures are in place on this Web site to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We offer industry-standard security measures available through your Web browser. When you are on this Web site, the sensitive information you provide such as credit card and financial information is encrypted with secure socket layer (SSL) technology and scrambled en route and decoded once it reaches us. No method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Please remember that e-mail, which is different from the encrypted sessions above, is not secure. Therefore, we ask that you do not send sensitive information such as credit card or account numbers to us via an unsecured e-mail message.

Information you provide will be safeguarded according to strict standards of security and confidentiality. We recognize and appreciate the importance of responsible use of the information you choose to provide. We take steps to require that our vendors, consultants, suppliers, and contractors observe our Privacy Policy with respect to security and the collection, use, and exchange of our customers' information. They are expected to abide by the Privacy Policy when conducting work for us and are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

## Tracking Activity on our Website 

In order to make your visit to our website as productive as possible, we track certain user activity. However, we want you to know that the tracking technology we use does not identify any personal information about you. It cannot retrieve data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or capture any personal information about you, such as your name, address, phone number, or email address. We only know who you are if you tell us.

As is true with most websites, we gather certain information automatically when individuals browse our site and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this non-personal information to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole, in order to improve the functionality of the website. We use a third-party tracking service that uses technology to track this non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate.

We use cookies to improve your shopping experience. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your web browser on your computer's hard drive. A cookie may contain information (such as a unique user session ID) that is used to track the pages of the websites you've visited. The information in cookies helps to serve you better by keeping track of your order when shopping on this site; it also helps us improve site design. We do not store sensitive information, other than your name, in your cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can set your browser to decline cookies. Even if your web browser is set to decline cookies, you can use many of the features within this site. However, you will not be able to place an order or retrieve your order status.

Some of our business partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site to help us manage the content on our site as well as to manage our advertising on other sites. The technologies may be used to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other sites to provide you targeted advertising based on your interests. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages. The information gathered by web beacons is not tied to our customers’ personally identifiable information. However, if you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by [clicking here](https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/).

Google Analytics is a specific technology used on this web site to manage content and advertising. You can find out how Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites at [this link ](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

## Social Media 

Our site may use social media features such as Facebook “like” and “Share This” buttons. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Children Visiting our Websites

This website is directed at adults. We do not knowingly collect or use information from children. Should children access this Web site, we are confident that parents will not judge any of the information provided as objectionable for viewing. If you are under 18, you may use this Web site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

## Other Websites Linked to our Websites

We are not responsible for the content or information practices employed by other websites that are linked to or from this website. In most cases, links to websites that are not Direct Checks Unlimited Sales, Inc. websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of this website.

## Consent to Privacy Policy/Changes to Privacy Policy

By using this website, you consent to our posted Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use this website. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Your continued use of this website following the posting of changes to these terms means that you accept these changes.

We may change our privacy policy at any time. Any changes to the privacy and security policy will be posted on this website so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it, as well as the latest updates on how we maintain the secure portions of our website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the changes becoming effective.

Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the confidentiality of information. These reviews are conducted by internal staff who report directly to the Board of Directors, external auditing and accounting firms, and government regulators. Included in these self-assessments and examinations are reviews of the controls and safeguards related to consumer privacy described in our Privacy Policy.

## Contacting Us 

We are committed to ensuring that the information we obtain and use is accurate. Please use the contact information below to update or correct the personally identifiable information that was collected online from you or to express choices about how we use your information for marketing purposes.

Direct Checks Unlimited Sales, Inc.

Dept. OPT, P.O. Box 35350

Colorado Springs, CO 80935-9850

1-866-449-8804

[Direct Checks Unlimited Sales, Inc. is a BBB accredited business] and complies with BBBOnLine standards. [[Click to verify our BBB accreditation and to see a current BBB report](http://www.bbb.org/minnesota/business-reviews/checks-printing/direct-to-consumer-in-colorado-springs-co-96353108 "Click to verify BBB accreditation and to see a BBB report").]
